Welcome back. In this lesson,
欢迎回来在这节课
we're going to tell you all about volatility.
我们将介绍波动率
Volatility is an important measure of risk, but what is risk?
波动率是衡量风险的重要方式 什么是风险？
We've talked a little about it already,
我们之前已经提到过
and you may have an intuitive idea for what it means.
你可能对风险有直观的概念
It's basically uncertainty about the future and in particular,
风险是指对未来不确定
uncertainty about bad things happening,
尤其是不确定是否会发生糟糕的事
like losing all the money you've invested in something.
例如损失所有的投资金额
In finance, risks can be thought of as uncertainty about future returns.
在金融领域 风险可以看做对未来收益不确定
Uncertainty, that sounds kind of hard to measure.
不确定听起来有点难衡量
How do you measure what you don't know?
如何衡量未知的事物？
Well, we can get started by thinking of the log return as
首先可以将对数收益率看做随机变量
a random variable that can assume different values with different probabilities.
它会以不同的概率成为不同的值
An important way of characterizing
描述概率分布的一个重要方式是
a probability distribution is with it's expected or mean value.
使用预期值或均值
The mean is the average of many measurements of the random variable,
均值是指随机变量的很多测量值的平均值
and you already know that
你已经知道
the standard deviation is a measure of the spread of a distribution.
标准差表示分布的分散性
Volatility is simply the standard deviation of
波动率等于
the probability distribution of log returns.
对数收益率的概率分布的标准差
It's a measure of the spread of this particular distribution.
它衡量的是这个分布的分散性
It measures the dispersion of log returns around the expected log return.
即对数收益率围绕预期对数收益率的离散情况
Volatility gives you a sense of the range of values log returns are likely to fall into.
波动率表示对数收益率可能的值范围
For example, say you measured log returns on
例如 假设你测量了
investment for several years and found that they happen
某个投资多年来的对数收益率
to be distributed more or less normally with a mean or expected log return of about 5%,
发现它们的分布比较正态 均值或预期对数收益率约为 5%
and an annual volatility of about 6%.
年度波动率约为 6%
If you remember, that for a normal distribution,
对于正态分布
about 95% of observations fall in a range from
约 95% 的观察值落入均值的
negative two to positive two standard deviations around the mean.
-2*标准差到 2*标准差范围内
This would mean that 95% of the annual returns would
表示 95% 的年度收益率
be between approximately negative 7% and positive 17%.
在约 -7% 到 17% 之间
So, why spend all this time learning about volatility?
为何要花大量时间学习波动率 ？
Basically, every investor trying to
每个投资者
understand what level of return they can expect to get on
既想知道平均会获得什么水平的收益率
average will also care about how often and by
又关心收益率与该平均值不同的
how much their returns are going to differ from that average.
概率和幅度是多少
In essence, volatility is a simple metric that characterizes variability in returns,
总之 波动率简单地衡量了收益率的变化性
that has many different users all over the financial world.
在金融世界有很多不同的用途
Let's list a few examples of the ways you might see it used.
下面介绍波动率的几个用途
As I said, volatility is one way to measure risk.
正如我所说的 波动率可以衡量风险
Traders can use volatility of
交易者可以根据交易工具的波动率
a trading instrument to define position sizing in a portfolio.
确定投资组合的头寸大小
Volatility can be used in the design of alphas, that is,
可以根据波动率设计 alpha
as part of the logic that defines which stocks to trade and when to trade them.
即确定交易哪些股票 何时交易
Volatility is very important for determining the prices of options contracts.
在确定期权合约的价格时 波动率很重要
Finally, it's possible to trade volatility directly.
最后 可以直接交易波动率
For example, you can trade an instrument that tracks the volatility of the S&amp;P 500,
例如 你可以交易一个跟踪标普 500 波动率的工具
we'll learn a little more about this later on.
稍后我们会详细讲解的